listitsellit.us 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy - List it Sell it Classifieds

Privacy Policy

Within the Privacy Policy, the Web site ("List it Sell It .us") will be referred to as "Company", "we" or "us". We are committed to complete permission-based marketing, while safeguarding your privacy online. Please read our privacy policy ("Policy") to understand how your personal information will be treated as submitted on the Website. This Policy also applies to individuals who have agreed to receive email marketing from the Company through opt-in or opt-out registration on another Website.

Where we collect your information

We collect information in several ways from different parts of the Website. From the visitors to our Website, we track domain, host, and/or Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Some personally identifiable information is gathered when you register in part or in full for one of our many services or promotions. Registration with the Website is required to participate in any promotions or sweepstakes at the Website. We may allow you to co-register (simultaneous registration with another third party Website and our Website) to participate in some of our services and promotions or those of third party Websites, as well. During registration, we may ask for information such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone numbers and the like.

We may also ask you for personally identifiable information at other times, including when you report a problem with the Website. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence, as well. From time to time, the Company may ask users to complete surveys that we use for research or other purposes. We may also offer users the opportunity to utilize other resources, services, forms, or tools, from which we may also collect your personal information.

Cookies

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, the Company may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. In addition, we may use pixel tags (also knows as clear gifs) to track some of the pages you visit on our website.

Use of personal information

By registering with our Website, completing any forms on our Website, or by checking or not unchecking co-registration boxes, you grant the Company the right to use the collected information for marketing purposes including, but not limited to, sharing such information with third party advertisers ("Advertisers"), emailing, or physically mailing Company or any third party offers to your email address or postal address. We may also use such information to fulfill prizes, track compliance with the applicable sweepstakes or promotion rules, or for content improvement and feedback purposes. We may sell the personal information that you supply to us and we may join together with other businesses to bring selected retail or service opportunities to our user base. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation. In addition, the Company reserves the right to release current or past user information in the event we believe that the Website is being or has been used in violation of any sweepstakes or promotion rules; to commit unlawful acts; if the information is subpoenaed; if the Company is sold or acquired; or when the Company deems it necessary or appropriate. By agreeing to these terms, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when the Company, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate.

We may share Website usage information about our Website visitors who have received targeted promotional campaigns with Advertisers for the purpose of formatting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics.

The Company also reserves the right to provide aggregate or group data about our visitors and users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage, or characteristics of our participants as a group, without revealing any personally identifiable information. By subscribing to the Website, you agree to allow us to provide such data to third parties.

Acceptance of Policy

By accessing this Website and/or submitting any information to us, you agree to this policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. All Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Therefore, you should check this page regularly to review the in effect Policy at that time. Your continued use of the Website or acceptance of our emails following the posting of changes to this Policy will mean that you accept these changes. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not submit any personal information on this or any Company Websites.
